(Sheldon:)Are you bringing
flowers to a patient
(Sheldon:)to cushion the blow of
a terminal diagnosis?
(laughs)
(Sheldon:)That wasn't a joke.
(Man:)All right.
(Man:)These are actually
for a nice woman
(Man:)who makes sales
calls to my office.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)You know, they have
delivery people
(Sheldon:)that will do that
for you.
(Man:)I was hoping
to impress her
(Man:)by tracking her down
on the Internet
(Man:)and then showing up
unannounced at her door.
(Sheldon:)Making the extra effort.
(Sheldon:)Good for you.
(Leonard:)Great timing,
food just got here.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, Siam Palace?
Yes.
(Sheldon:)Uh, mee krob and chicken satay?
(Sheldon:)Uh, extra peanut sauce?
No, but you can have mine.
(Sheldon:)Eh, well, very well.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and on the topic of
sharing things that are yours,